http://www.memorialwoodlands.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy:
Memorial Woodlands ("Memorial Woodlands")
operates memorialwoodlands.com and may operate other websites. It
is Memorial Woodlands' policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect
while operating our websites.
Website Visitors
Like most website operators, Memorial Woodlands collects non-personally-identifying information of the
sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference,
referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Memorial Woodlands' purpose in
collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand
how Memorial Woodlands' visitors use its website. From time to
time, Memorial Woodlands may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by
publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.
Memorial Woodlands also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol
(IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on memorialwoodlands.com
blogs/sites. Memorial Woodlands only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same
circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that
commenter IP addresses and email addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog/site
where the comment was left.
Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information
Certain visitors to Memorial Woodlands' websites choose to interact
with Memorial Woodlands in ways that require Memorial Woodlands to gather
personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Memorial Woodlands gathers
depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up at memorialwoodlands.com to provide a
username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with Memorial Woodlands are asked to
provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to
process those transactions. In each case, Memorial Woodlands collects such information only insofar as
is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor's interaction with
Memorial Woodlands. Memorial Woodlands does not disclose personally-identifying information
other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with
the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.
Aggregated Statistics
Memorial Woodlands may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its
websites. Memorial Woodlands may display this information publicly or provide it to others.
However, Memorial Woodlands does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as
described below.
Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information
Memorial Woodlands discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information
only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information
in order to process it on Memorial Woodlands' behalf or to provide services available
at Memorial Woodlands' websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some
of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by
using Memorial Woodlands' websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to
them. Memorial Woodlands will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and
personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated
organizations, as described above, Memorial Woodlands discloses potentially personally-identifying and
personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or
when Memorial Woodlands believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the
property or rights of Memorial Woodlands, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered
user of an Memorial Woodlands website and have supplied your email address, Memorial Woodlands
may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to
date with what's going on with Memorial Woodlands and our products. If you send us a request (for
example via email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us
clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Memorial Woodlands takes all
measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of
potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.
Cookies
A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser
provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Memorial Woodlands uses cookies to
help Memorial Woodlands identify and track visitors, their usage of Memorial Woodlands
website, and their website access preferences. Memorial Woodlands visitors who do not wish to have
cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before
using Memorial Woodlands' websites, with the drawback that certain features
of Memorial Woodlands' websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.
Business Transfers
If Memorial Woodlands, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event
that Memorial Woodlands goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the
assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that
any acquirer of Memorial Woodlands may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this
policy.
Ads
Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies.
These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to
compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among
other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy
Policy covers the use of cookies by Memorial Woodlands and does not cover the use of cookies by any
advertisers.
Privacy Policy Changes
Although most changes are likely to be minor, Memorial Woodlands may change
its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Memorial Woodlands' sole
discretion. Memorial Woodlands encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to
its Privacy Policy. If you have a memorialwoodlands.com account, you might also
receive an alert informing you of these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in
this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
This website uses cookies to improve your experience. We'll assume you're ok with this, but you can opt-out if you wish.Accept Read MorePrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close
Necessary
Always Enabled
COVID-19 UpdateCOVID-19 StatementWe are keeping up to date with the latest government guidance on funerals in lockdown status. No matter the lockdowns and restrictions, we are here to help you 24 hours a day, 7 days a week.
See below for advice on arranging and attending a funeral.
Please call our team on 01454 414 999 for and information or support.
Last updated: Wednesday 2nd December 2020
Please read our full COVID-19 Infection Control Arrangements here.
